Student Newspapers; Collection ua809
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- State College News, 1930s, 1930-1939; 3; 280 Digital Files
  - State College News, 1936, 27 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 21, Number 11, 1936 December 11; 7.89 MB
  - State College News, 1937, 24 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 21, Number 12, 1937 January 8; 7.52 MB
    - State College News, Volume 21, Number 13, 1937 January 15; 10.03 MB
    - State College News, Volume 21, Number 14, 1937 February 12; 3.35 MB
    - State College News, Volume 21, Number 15, 1937 February 19; 10.59 MB
    - State College News, Volume 21, Number 16, 1937 February 26; 5.23 MB
    - State College News, Volume 21, Number 17, 1937 March 12; 10.72 MB
    - State College News, Volume, Number 18, 1937 March 19; 5.07 MB
    - State College News, Volume 21, Number 19, 1937 April 9; 4.89 MB
    - State College News, Volume 21, Number 20, 1937 April 16; 5.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 21, Number 21, 1937 April 23; 10.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 21, Number 22, 1937 May 7; 15.82 MB
    - State College News, Volume 21, Number 23, 1937 May 20; 4.76 MB
    - State College News, Volume 21, Number 24, 1937 May 28; 11.45 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 1, 1937 September 24; 5.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 2, 1937 October 1; 5.89 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 3, 1937 October 8; 5.80 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 4, 1937 October 15; 5.42 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 5, 1937 October 22; 5.43 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 6, 1937 October 29; 5.23 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 7, 1937 November 5; 5.17 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 8, 1937 November 12; 5.38 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 9, 1937 November 19; 5.73 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 10, 1937 December 3; 5.59 MB
    - State College News, volume 22, Number 11, 1937 December 10; 4.64 MB
  - State College News, 1938, 27 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 12, 1938 January 7; 4.73 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 13, 1938 January 14; 5.56 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 14, 1938 February 11; 7.06 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 15, 1938 February 19; 5.65 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 16, 1938 February 25; 5.97 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 17, 1938 March 4; 5.89 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 18, 1938 March 11; 5.42 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 19, 1938 March 18; 5.27 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 20, 1938 March 25; 5.83 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 21, 1938 April 1; 5.66 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 22, 1938 April 8; 7.55 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 23, 1938 April 19; 5.61 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 24, 1938 May 6; 5.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 25, 1938 May 13; 5.06 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 26, 1938 May 19; 4.98 MB
    - State College News, Volume 22, Number 27, 1938 May 27; 44.86 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 1, 1938 September 23; 4.71 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 2, 1938 September 30; 5.33 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 3, 1938 October 7; 5.34 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 4, 1938 October 14; 12.78 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 5, 1938 October 28; 14.58 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 6, 1938 November 4; 11.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 7, 1938 November 11; 5.37 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 8, 1938 November 18; 5.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 9, 1938 December 2; 12.60 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 10, 1938 December 9; 5.22 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 11, 1938 December 16; 4.28 MB
  - State College News, 1939, 33 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 12, 1939 January 6; 4.80 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 13, 1939 January 13; 5.86 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 14, 1939 January 20; 5.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 15, 1939 February 10; 6.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 16, 1939 February 17; 12.95 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 17, 1939 February 24; 13.06 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 18, 1939 March 10; 5.54 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 19, 1939 March 17; 5.45 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 20, 1939 March 24; 11.93 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 21, 1939 March 31; 13.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 22, 1939 April 21; 5.85 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 23, 1939 April 24; 3.58 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 24, 1939 April 28; 13.08 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 25, 1939 May 12; 16.55 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 26, 1939 May 18; 12.88 MB
    - State College News, Volume 23, Number 27, 1939 May 26; 5.22 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 1, 1939 July 14; 3.64 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 2, 1939 July 21; 2.13 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 3, 1939 July 24; 3.72 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 4, 1939 August 4; 3.59 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 5, 1939 August 11; 2.85 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 1, 1939 September 22; 10.09 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 2, 1939 September 29; 5.36 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 3, 1939 October 6; 5.59 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 4, 1939 October 13; 12.59 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 5, 1939 October 20; 7.66 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 6, 1939 October 27; 5.56 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 7, 1939 November 3; 5.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 8, 1939 November 10; 5.88 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 9, 1939 November 17; 5.69 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 10, 1939 December 1; 5.52 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 11, 1939 December 8; 5.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 12, 1939 December 15; 4.14 MB
- State College News, 1940s, 1940-1949; 4; 263 Digital Files
  - State College News, 1940, 24 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 13, 1940 January 5; 4.73 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 14, 1940 January 12; 7.88 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 15, 1940 February 9; 5.66 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 16, 1940 February 16; 6.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 17, 1940 February 23; 5.77 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 18, 1940 March 1; 5.62 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 19, 1940 March 8; 5.58 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 20, 1940 April 12; 5.66 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 21, 1940 April 19; 5.50 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 22, 1940 May 3; 5.18 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 23, 1940 May 16; 5.34 MB
    - State College News, Volume 24, Number 24, 1940 May 24; 4.71 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 1, 1940 September 20; 5.04 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 2, 1940 September 27; 5.93 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 3, 1940 October 4; 6.27 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 4, 1940 October 11; 6.01 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 5, 1940 October 18; 6.06 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 6, 1940 October 25; 6.02 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 7, 1940 November 1; 5.96 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 8, 1940 November 8; 5.90 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 9, 1940 November 15; 5.93 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 10, 1940 November 29; 5.96 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 11, 1940 December 6; 5.72 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 12, 1940 December 13; 4.78 MB
  - State College News, 1941, 28 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 13, 1941 January 10; 6.72 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 14, 1941 February 7; 6.14 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 15, 1941 February 14; 6.11 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 16, 1941 February 20; 7.10 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 17, 1941 February 28; 5.94 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 18, 1941 March 7; 5.66 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 19, 1941 March 14; 5.71 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 20, 1941 March 21; 5.98 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 21, 1941 March 28; 5.82 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 22, 1941 April 3; 13.03 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 23, 1941 April 25; 5.98 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 24, 1941 May 2; 5.70 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 25, 1941 May 9; 5.60 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 26, 1941 May 15; 5.74 MB
    - State College News, Volume 25, Number 27, 1941 May 23; 4.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 1, 1941 September 19; 7.16 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 2, 1941 September 26; 13.10 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 3, 1941 October 3; 17.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 4, 1941 October 10; 7.55 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 5, 1941 October 17; 13.55 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 6, 1941 October 24; 8.06 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 7, 1941 October 31; 5.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 8, 1941 November 7; 7.87 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 9, 1941 November 14; 5.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 10, 1941 November 28; 7.97 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 11, 1941 December 5; 7.97 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 12, 1941 December 12; 6.37 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 13, 1941 December 19; 12.82 MB
  - State College News, 1942, 29 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 14, 1942 January 9; 5.07 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 15, 1942 January 30; 6.24 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 16, 1942 February 6; 6.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 17, 1942 February 13; 6.16 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 18, 1942 February 20; 15.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 19, 1942 February 27; 6.11 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 20, 1942 March 6; 6.55 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 21, 1942 March 12; 6.25 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 22, 1942 March 20; 6.17 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 23, 1942 April 10; 7.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 24, 1942 April 17; 8.17 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 25, 1942 April 24; 5.70 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 26, 1942 May 1; 7.49 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 27, 1942 May 8; 7.79 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 28, 1942 May 9; 3.87 MB
    - State College News, Volume 26, Number 29, 1942 May 15; 4.94 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 1, 1942 September 18; 5.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 2, 1942 September 25; 6.28 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 3, 1942 October 2; 6.12 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 4, 1942 October 9; 6.19 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 5, 1942 October 16; 6.03 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 6, 1942 October 23; 6.20 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 7, 1942 October 30; 5.99 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 8, 1942 November 6; 5.94 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 9, 1942 November 13; 5.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 10, 1942 November 20; 5.71 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 11, 1942 December 4; 5.24 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 12, 1942 December 11; 5.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 13, 1942 December 17; 4.30 MB
  - State College News, 1943, 28 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 14, 1943 January 8; 4.32 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 15, 1943 February 5; 6.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 16, 1943 February 12; 5.78 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 17, 1943 February 19; 5.27 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 18, 1943 February 26; 5.16 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 19, 1943 March 5; 5.78 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 20, 1943 March 12; 5.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 21, 1943 March 19; 5.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 22, 1943 March 26; 5.33 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 23, 1943 April 16; 5.36 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 24, 1943 April 22; 5.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 25, 1943 April 30; 5.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 26, 1943 May 7; 7.20 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 27, 1943 May 8; 3.02 MB
    - State College News, Volume 27, Number 28, 1943 May 14; 4.04 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 1, 1943 September 17; 4.90 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 2, 1943 September 24; 5.86 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 3, 1943 October 1; 6.06 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 4, 1943 October 8; 6.05 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 5, 1943 October 15; 6.13 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 6, 1943 October 22; 5.96 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 7, 1943 October 29; 5.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 8, 1943 November 5; 5.57 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 9, 1943 November 12; 5.78 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 10, 1943 November 19; 5.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 11, 1943 December 3; 5.80 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 12, 1943 December 10; 5.92 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 13, 1943 December 16; 4.67 MB
  - State College News, 1944, 27 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 14, 1944 January 7; 4.83 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 15, 1944 January 14; 6.05 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 16, 1944 February 14; 5.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 17, 1944 February 25; 5.91 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 18, 1944 March 2; 5.87 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 19, 1944 March 10; 5.87 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 20, 1944 March 17; 5.94 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 21, 1944 March 24; 5.72 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 22, 1944 March 31; 5.83 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 23, 1944 April 21; 5.74 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 24, 1944 April 29; 5.74 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 25, 1944 May 4; 8.49 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 26, 1944 May 9; 3.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 27, 1944 May 12; 5.15 MB
    - State College News, Volume 28, Number 28, 1944 May 19; 4.59 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 1, 1944 September 15; 5.74 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 2, 1944 September 22; 6.74 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 3, 1944 September 29; 6.79 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 4, 1944 October 6; 6.71 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 5, 1944 October 13; 6.69 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 6, 1944 October 27; 6.57 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 7, 1944 November 3; 6.24 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 8, 1944 November 10; 6.48 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 9, 1944 November 17; 6.38 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 10, 1944 December 1; 6.43 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 11, 1944 December 8; 6.49 MB
    - State College News, volume 29, Number 12, 1944 December 15; 5.44 MB
  - State College News, 1945, 26 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 13, 1945 January 12; 5.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 14, 1945 February 9; 6.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 15, 1945 February 16; 6.38 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 16, 1945 February 23; 6.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 17, 1945 March 9; 6.10 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 18, 1945 March 16; 6.23 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 19, 1945 March 23; 6.36 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 20, 1945 April 13; 7.13 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 21, 1945 April 20; 7.13 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 22, 1945 April 27; 6.96 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 23, 1945 May 4; 7.11 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 24, 1945 May 10; 7.24 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 25, 1945 May 11; 4.16 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 26, 1945 May 18; 6.43 MB
    - State College News, Volume 29, Number 27, 1945 May 25; 5.93 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 1, 1945 September 21; 5.35 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 2, 1945 September 28; 6.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 3, 1945 October 8; 6.33 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 4, 1945 October 12; 4.52 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 5, 1945 October 19; 6.92 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 6, 1945 October 26; 8.69 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 7, 1945 November 2; 6.36 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 8, 1945 November 9; 8.73 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 9, 1945 November 16; 6.69 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 10, 1945 November 30; 6.48 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 11, 1945 December 7; 9.66 MB
  - State College News, 1946, 26 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 13, 1946 January 11; 7.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 14, 1946 February 8; 6.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 15, 1946 February 15; 6.35 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 16, 1946 February 22; 6.10 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 17, 1946 March 1; 6.28 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 18, 1946 March 8; 6.01 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 19, 1946 March 15; 6.13 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 20, 1946 March 22; 7.99 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 21, 1946 March 29; 6.08 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 22, 1946 April 9; 6.42 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 23, 1946 April 12; 6.34 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 24, 1946 April 26; 4.18 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 25, 1946 May 3; 8.35 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 26, 1946 May 9; 4.51 MB
    - State College News, Volume 30, Number 27, 1946 May 17; 6.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 1, 1946 September 20; 5.58 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 2, 1946 September 27; 6.22 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 3, 1946 October 4; 8.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 4, 1946 October 18; 6.31 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 5, 1946 October 25; 8.59 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 6, 1946 November 1; 7.22 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 7, 1946 November 8; 6.78 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 8, 1946 November 15; 8.61 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 9, 1946 November 22; 8.41 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 9, 1946 December 6; 6.33 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 10, 1946 December 13; 7.18 MB
  - State College News, 1947, 27 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 11, 1947 January 9; 6.89 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 12, 1947 January 10; 7.96 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 13, 1947 February 7; 6.18 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 14, 1947 February 14; 6.20 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 15, 1947 February 21; 8.42 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 16, 1947 February 28; 6.27 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 17, 1947 March 7; 6.10 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 18, 1947 March 14; 8.12 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 19, 1947 March 21; 5.95 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 20, 1947 March 28; 5.95 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 21, 1947 April 18; 7.97 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 22, 1947 April 25; 8.17 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 23, 1947 May 2; 7.77 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 24, 1947 May 8; 5.52 MB
    - State College News, Volume 31, Number 25, 1947 May 9; 2.58 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 1, 1947 September 19; 5.06 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 2, 1947 September 28; 7.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 3, 1947 October 3; 5.16 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 4, 1947 October 10; 7.73 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 5, 1947 October 17; 5.37 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 6, 1947 October 24; 7.18 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 7, 1947 October 31; 7.54 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 8, 1947 November 7; 6.97 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 9, 1947 November 14; 5.15 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 10, 1947 November 21; 7.05 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 11, 1947 December 3; 7.26 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 12, 1947 December 12; 6.25 MB
  - State College News, 1948, 24 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 14, 1948 February 6; 5.92 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 15, 1948 February 13; 5.52 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 16, 1948 February 20; 7.23 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 18, 1948 March 5; 7.52 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 19, 1948 March 12; 7.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 20, 1948 March 19; 7.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 21, 1948 April 9; 7.37 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 22, 1948 April 16; 6.92 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 23, 1948 April 23; 7.23 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 24, 1948 April 30; 6.91 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 25, 1948 May 6; 5.22 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 26, 1948 May 7; 4.62 MB
    - State College News, Volume 32, Number 27, 1948 May 14; 5.85 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 1, 1948 September 24; 4.83 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 2, 1948 October 1; 5.64 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 3, 1948 October 8; 5.60 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 4, 1948 October 15; 5.70 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 5, 1948 October 22; 7.82 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 6, 1948 October 29; 7.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 7, 1948 November 5; 7.80 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 8, 1948 November 12; 7.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 9, 1948 November 19; 7.52 MB